Guide to the Union for Radical Political Economics and Review of radical political economics records, 1961-2013.
Union for Radical Political Economics and Review of radical political economics records, 1961-2013
- Series I. Articles Submitted for Publication in RRPE
  - Subseries B: Numbered Articles Submitted And Accepted, (originally submitted to specific RRPE issues)
    - #2813 - Chen, Ying. "Are Chinese Workers Paid the Correct Wages?", 2013 (Box 35, Folder 79)
    - #2906 - Zhou, Yi. "Tragedy of Anticommons in Knowledge", 2013 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - #2787 - Lambert, Thomas. "Top One Percent and Exploitation Measures", 2013 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - #2847b - Reviewed by O'Hara, Phillip. "Capital, Economic Crises, Institutions and History", 2013 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - #2885b - Reviewed by Gurcan, Efe. "Capitalist Class Formation and U.S. Imperialism", 2013 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - #2925b - Reviewed by Van Der Veen, Marjolein. "The Making of Global Capitalism", 2013 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - #2920b - Reviewed by Bolukoglu, Anil. "Contemporary Capitalism and Its Crises", 2013 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - #2938b - Reviewed by DiQuattro, Arthur. "Socialist Alternative", 2013 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - #2946b - Reviewed by Fox, Kenneth. "The Price of Inequality", 2013 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - #2888 - Lipow, Gar. "Shutting Down the Fog Machine", 2013 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - #3002 - Harcourt, Geoff. "Marginal Productivity Theory of Distribution", 2014 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - #3028 - Lazzarini, Andres. "Some Unsettled Issues in a Second Phase of the Cambridge-Cambridge Controversy", 2014 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - #3006 - McCombie, John. "Can the Marginal Productivity Theory of Distribution Be Tested?, 2014 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - #3007 - Moseley, Fred. "The Marginal Productivity Theory of Capital in Intermediate Microeconomnics Textbooks:, 2014 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - #2975 - Hahnel, Robin. Response to Lipow on Climate Change Policy, 2014 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - #2956b - Reviewed by Levenstein, Charles. "Trade Unions and the Green Economy", 2014 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - #3011b - Reviewed by de Kadt, Maarten. "Two View on Urban Revolution", 2014 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - #3025b - Reviewed by Andrews, Charles. "Capital in the Twenty-First Century", 2014 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - #3022b - Reviewed by Birks, Stuart. "Challenging the Orthodoxy", 2013 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - #2978b - Reviewed by Dierckx, Sacha. "Reclaiming Public Ownership", 2014 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - #3034b - Reviewed by Pryke, Sam. "Never Let a Serious Crisis Go to Waste", 2014 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - #3983b - Reviewed by Gleicher, David. "From Austerity to Prosperity", 2014 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - #2976b - Reviewed by Scharber, Helen. "Ecological Economics from the Ground Up", 2014 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - #3007b - Reviewed by Coyle, Eugene. "The Problem with Work", 2014 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - #2986b - Reviewed by Panayotakis, Costas. "Unions and Class Transformation", 2014 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - #2860B - Reviewed by Argyrous, George. "Coming of Age of Information Technologies", 2014 (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - #2802 - Lara, Pedro. "Does a Democratic Model Enhance Performance Through Market Orientation?", 2014 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - #2990 - Obeng-Odoom, Franklin. "Property in the Commons: Origins and Paradigms", 2014 (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - #2987 - Austen, Giles. "Species Commodification - a Perspective on Fisheries Policy", 2014 (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - #2989 - North, Peter. "Rethinking the Factors of Production for a World of Common Ownership and Sustainability", 2014 (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - #2979 - Newman, Daniel. "The Car and the Commons", 2014 (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - #2992 - Dolenec, Danijela. "Exploring Commons Theory for Principles of a Socialist Governmentality", 2014 (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - #2969 - Gunn, Christopher. "Acequias as Commons: Lessons for a Post-Capitalist World", 2014 (Box 36, Folder 32)
    - #2993 - Euler, Johannes. "Commons-Creating Society: On the Radical German Commons Discourse", 2014 (Box 36, Folder 33)
    - #2895 - Dugger, Bill. "Technology and Property: Knowledge and the Commons", 2014 (Box 36, Folder 34)
    - #3010 - Dolcerocca, Antoine. "Commons and the Public Domain", 2014 (Box 36, Folder 35)
    - #2988 - Gonzalez, Pablo. "Knowledge Economy and the Commons", 2014 (Box 36, Folder 36)
    - #2980 - Sherman, Zoe. "Primitive Accumulation in the Cultural Commons", 2014 (Box 36, Folder 37)
    - #2940 - Seda-Irizarry, Ian. "Re-centering Class in Critical Theory", 2014 (Box 36, Folder 38)
    - #2951 - Jefferies, William. "On the Alleged Stagnation of Capitalism", 2014 (Box 36, Folder 39)
    - #2933 - Sandoval, Marisol. "From CSR to RSC - A Contribution to the Critique of the Political Economy of Corporate Social Responsibility", 2014 (Box 36, Folder 40)
    - #2924 - Bundey, Freya. "Financialized Household and the Consumer Price Index", 2014 (Box 36, Folder 41)
    - #2756 - Chiliatto-Leite, Marcos. "Fourth Dimension: Derivatives and Financial Dominance", 2014 (Box 36, Folder 42)
    - #2737 - Diop, Samba. "Minsky's Analysis of Capitalist Development", 2014 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - # 2738 - Obeng-Odoom, Franklin. "Understanding Land Reform in Ghana", 2014 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - # 2842 - Cooney, Paul. "Industrial Trajectory and Economic Development:, 2014 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - # 2845 - Kuchler, Magdalena. "Bioenergy as an Empty Signifier", 2014 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - # 2851 - Frerichs, Sabine. "Egypt's Neoliberal Reforms and the Moral Economy of Bread", 2014 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - # 2853 - Devetter, Francios-Xavier. "Can Public Policies Bring About the Democratization of the Outsourcing of Household Tasks?", 2014 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - # 2861 - Morente, Francisco. "Transformation of Values into Prices of Production in Marx's Scheme of Expanded Reproduction", 2014 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - # 2904 - Lievens, Matthias. "Greening the Economy or Economizing the Green Project?", 2014 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - # 2910 - Karachimen, Elif. "Consumer Credit as an Aspect of Everyday Life of Workers in Developing Countries", 2014 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - # 2953 - Kim, Joonil. "Does Shareholder Value Orientation or Financial Market Liberalization Slow Down Korean Real Investment?, 2014 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - # 2961 - Park, Hyeng-Joon. "Korea's Post-1997 Restructuring: An Analysis of Capital as Power", 2014 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - # 3000 - Oncu, Ahmet. "On the Possibility of a Soviet of Technicians", 2014 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - # 3004 - Susnik, Urban. "Janus Ante Portas: Distribution and Class Struggle in a Bank-Money World Model", 2014 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - # 3017 - Seretis, Stergios. "Absolute Advantage and International Trade: Evidence from Four Euro-zone Economics", 2014 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - # 3029 - Liagouras, George. "From Heterodox Political Economy to Generalized Darwinism", 2014 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - # 3039b - Reviewed by Brunstein, Luis. "Principles of Macroeconomics - Activist vs. Austerity Policies", 2014 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - # 3041b - Reviewed by Salazar, Sibyl. "Afterthoughts On Beyond Marx: Theorizing the Global Relations of the Twenty-First Century", 2014 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - # 3044b - Reviewed by Fuentes-Ramirez, Ricardo. "Cooperatives and Socialism: A View from Cuba", 2014 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - # 3047b - Reviewed by Zarembka, Paul. "The Complete Works of Rosa Luxemburg", 2014 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - # 3050b - Reviewed by Wilson, Tamar. "Social Conflict, Economic Development and Extractive Industry: Evidence from South America", 2014 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - # 3053b - Reviewed by Lapegna, Pablo. "Seeds, Science and Struggle", 2014 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - # 3056b - Reviewed by Keaney, Michael. "Globalization, Hegemony and the Future of the City of London", 2014 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - # 3061b - Reviewed by Major, Aaron. "Beyond Capitalism: Building Democratic Alternatives for Today and the Future", 2014 (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - # 3068b - Reviewed by Ragusett, Jared. "Subprime Cities: The Political Economy of Mortgage Markets", 2014 (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - # 2839 - Patroni, Viviana. "Precarious Work in Recession and Growth: New Structural Feature of Labor Markets in Argentina", 2015 (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - # 2879 - Vera, Leonardo. "Distribution of Power and the Inflation-Unemployment Relationship in the U.S.", 2015 (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - # 2887 - Melmies, Jordan. "Industrial Seigniorage: The Other Face of Competition", 2015 (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - # 2893 - Skillman, Gilbert. "Production Relations in Agrarian Capitalist Development", 2015 (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - # 2923 - Santarcangelo, Juan. "Growth, Employment and Income distribution in Argentina, 1990-2010", 2015 (Box 39, Folder 29)
    - # 2945 - Kotarski, Kristijan. "Political Economy of Banking and Debt Crisis in the EU", 2015 (Box 39, Folder 30)
    - # 2982 - Nikiforos, Michalis. "Uncertainty and Contradiction: An Essay on the Business Cycle", 2015 (Box 39, Folder 31)
    - # 2984b - Reviewed by Bina, Cyrus. "No War for Oil", 2015 (Box 39, Folder 32)
    - # 2991 - Lapniewska, Zofia. "(Re)claiming Space by Urban Commons", 2015 (Box 39, Folder 33)
    - # 3005 - Wrenn, Mary. "Immanent Critique, Enabling Myths, and the Neoliberal Narrative", 2015 (Box 39, Folder 34)
    - # 3013 - Tsoulfidis, Lefteris. " Growth Accounting of the Value Composition of Capital and the Rate of Profit in the US Economy", 2015 (Box 39, Folder 35)
    - # 3016 - Jossa, Bruno. "In Historical Materialism a Deterministic Approach?", 2015 (Box 39, Folder 36)
    - # 3036 - Hahnel, Robin. "Wanted: A Pollution Damage Revealing Mechanism", 2015 (Box 39, Folder 37)
    - # 3037 - Hahnel, Robin. "A Tale of Three Theorems", 2015 (Box 39, Folder 38)
    - # 3042 - Cantillon, Sara. "The Political Economy Landscape: In Conversation with Nancy Folbre", 2015 (Box 39, Folder 39)
    - # 3049 - Lamarche, Thomas. "Does CSR Contribute to Sustainable Development?", 2015 (Box 39, Folder 40)
    - # 3057 - Hahnel, Robin. "Environmental Sustainability in a Sraffian Framework", 2015 (Box 39, Folder 41)
    - # 3060 - Guizzo, Danielle. "Polanyi and Foucault on the Issue of Market in Classical Political Economy", 2015 (Box 39, Folder 42)
    - # 3062 - Montes-Rojas, Gabriel. "A Capital Invariant Solution to the Marxian Transformation Problem", 2015 (Box 39, Folder 43)
    - # 3064 - Reitz, Charles. "Accounting for Inequality: Questioning Piketty on National Income accounting and the Capital Labor Split", 2015 (Box 39, Folder 44)
    - # 3066 - Fuentes-Ramirez, Ricardo. "Economic Stages and Anti-Imperialism in Theory and Practice", 2015 (Box 39, Folder 45)
    - # 3077 - Marchionatti, Roberto. "On the Theoretical and Practical Relevance of the Concept of Gift to the Development of a Non-Imperialist Economics", 2015 (Box 39, Folder 46)
    - # 3079b - Reviewed by Leitch, Richy. "Solidarity", 2015 (Box 39, Folder 47)
    - # 3080 - Roncolato, Leanne. "Job Quality Complexities: Self-employment Within the Low-income Communities Surrounding Cape Town, South Africa", 2015 (Box 39, Folder 48)
    - # 3081b - Reviewed by Weisskopf, Thomas. "The Power of Market Fundamentalism", 2015 (Box 39, Folder 49)
    - # 3082 - Lampa, Roberto. "Crisis in Venezuela, or the Bolivarian Dilemma" r, 2015 (Box 39, Folder 50)
    - # 3085b - Reviewed by Lafferty, George. "Homo Economicus, Moral Sentiments and the Challenges of Individualism", 2015 (Box 39, Folder 51)
    - # 3087 - Sharzer, Greg. "Co-operatives as Transitional Economics", 2015 (Box 39, Folder 52)
    - # #113b - Reviewed by Takeda, Hiroko. "The Great Transformation of Japanese Capitalism", 2015 (Box 39, Folder 53)
    - # 3114b - Reviewed by Goldsmith, William. "Corporate Power, Oligopolies and the Crisis of the State", 2015 (Box 39, Folder 54)
    - # 3123b - Reviewed by Nwoke, Chibuzo. "Oiling the Urban Economy: Land, Labour, Capital and the State in Sekondi-Takoradi, Ghana", 2015 (Box 39, Folder 55)
    - # 3124 - Karak, Anirban. "Accumulation by Dispossession: A Marxist History of the Formation of the English Premier League", 2015 (Box 39, Folder 56)
    - # 3126b - Reviewed by Lambert, Thomas. "The Aggregate Production Function and the Measurement of Technical Change", 2015 (Box 39, Folder 57)
    - # 3127b - Reviewed by Avsar, Rojhat. "The Fair Society: The Science of Human Nature and the Pursuit of Social Justice", 2015 (Box 39, Folder 58)
    - # 3129b - Reviewed by Prince, Heath. "The Political Economy of Development: The World Bank, Neoliberalism and Development Research", 2015 (Box 39, Folder 59)
    - # 3130 - Kadt, Maarten. "Worldview Matters", 2015 (Box 39, Folder 60)
    - # 3136b - Reviewed by Tabb, William. "Global Capitalism", 2015 (Box 39, Folder 61)
    - # 3145b - Reviewed by Page-Hoongrajok, Amanda. "What Then Must We do? Straight Talk About the Next American Revolution", 2015 (Box 39, Folder 62)
    - # 3151b - Reviewed by Weisskopf, Thomas. "The Fracturing of the American Corporate Elite", 2015 (Box 39, Folder 63)
    - # 3157b - Reviewed by Freidman, Gerald. "What Every Economics Student Needs to Know and Doesn't Get in the Usual Principles Text", 2015 (Box 39, Folder 64)
    - WAPE - Yoshihara, Naoki. ""Exploitation of Labour and Exploitation of Commodities", 2011 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - WAPE - Skott, Peter. "Increasing Inequality and Financial Instability", 2011 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - WAPE - Laibman, David. "Mature Socialism: Design, Prerequisites, Transitions", 2011 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - WAPE - Haight, Alan. "The Intolerance Multiplier: A Diagram", 2012 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - WAPE - Moseley, Fred. "The U.S. Economic Crisis", 2012 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - WAPE - Stenn, Tamara. "Comercio Justo and Justice: An Examination of Fair Trade", 2012 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - WAPE - Duggan, Marie. "Taking Back Globalization", 2012 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - WAPE - Mikotz, David. "Introduction To The Special Issue of RRPE of Papers from the WAPE Forum", 2012 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - WAPE - Li, Zhongjin. "Can the Socialist Market Economy in China Adhere to Socialism?", 2012 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - WAPE - Piovani, Chiara. "Climate Change and the Limits to the Growth-Oriented Model of Development", 2012 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - WAPE - Seifert, Roger. "Neo-Liberalism at Work", 2012 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - WAPE - Izquierdo, Sergio. "Cyclical Decline of the Profit Rate as the Cause of Crises in the U.S.", 2012 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - ASSA - Colander, David. "Is the Fundamental Science of Macroeconomics Sound?", 2011 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - ASSA - Dutt, Amitava. "Macroeconomic Theory After the Crisis", 2011 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - ASSA - Gunn, Christopher. "Workers' Participation in Management, Workers' Control of Production", 2011 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - ASSA - Campbell, Al. "The Role of Workers in Management", 2011 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - ASSA - Ji, Minsun. "Global Restructuring, Social Distancing and a Community Strategy", 2011 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - ASSA - Goldstein,Jonathan. "Race in Early Tobacco Advertising: The Case of American Tobacco Cards", 2011 (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - ASSA - Kaboub, Fadhel. "From Neoliberalism to Social Justice", 2012 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - ASSA - Deere, Carmen and Twyman, Jennifer. "Asset Ownership and Egalitarian Decision Making in Dual Headed Households in Ecuador", 2012 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - ASSA - Murray, Michael. "Targeted Demand Management and the Employer of Last Resort Program", 2012 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - ASSA - Chaudhuri, Sanjukta. "Female Infant Mortality Disadvantage in India", 2012 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - ASSA - Prasch, Robert. "Neoliberalism and Ethnic Conflict", 2012 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - ASSA - Anderson, Bret. "Economic Growth and Employment From 1990-2010", 2013 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - ASSA - Kim, Marlene. "Policies to End the Gender Wage Gap in the United States", 2013 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - ASSA - Kotz, David. "The Current Economic Crisis in the UI.S.: A crisis of Over-Investment", 2013 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - ASSA - Kirdina, Svetlana. "New Systemic Institutinal Approach for Comparative Political and Economic Analysis", 2013 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - ASSA - Campbell, Al. "The Financial Rate of Profit: What is it, and How Has it Behaved in the U.S.", 2013 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - ASSA - Bracarense, Natalia. "Co ntact Zones: Development Theory and the Cultural Turn", 2013 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - ASSA - Faboub, Fadhel. "The Fiscal Cliff Mythology and the Full Employment Alternative", 2013 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - ASSA - Chester, Lynne. "The Failure of Market Fundamentalism: How Electricity Sector Restructuring is Threatening the Economic and Social Fabric"", 2013 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - ASSA - Skott, Peter. "Power, Luck and Ideology: Technological and Institutional Parameters of the agency Problem for CEO's", 2013 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - ASSA - Koechlin, Tim. "Urban Inequality, Neoliberalism and the Case for a Multidisciplinary Economics", 2014 (Box 36, Folder 45)
    - ASSA - Orhangazi, Ozgur. "Capitalism, Crisis and Class", 2014 (Box 36, Folder 46)
    - ASSA - Hossein-zadeh, Ismael. "Flaws in the Marxian Explanations of the Great Recession", 2014 (Box 36, Folder 47)
    - ASSA - Li, Zhongjin. "Labor Process and the Social Structure of Accumulation in China", 2014 (Box 36, Folder 48)
    - ASSA - Hewitson, Gilliam. "The Commodified Womb and Neoliberal Families", 2014 (Box 36, Folder 49)
    - ASSA - Kotz, David. "Capitalism and Forms of Capitalism", 2015 (Box 36, Folder 50)
    - ASSA - Bakir, Erdogan. "Is Over-Investment the Cause of the Post-2007 U.S. Economic Crisis?", 2015 (Box 36, Folder 51)
    - ASSA - Mongiovi, Gary, "Piketty on Capitalism and Inequality: A Radical Economics Perspective", 2015 (Box 36, Folder 52)
    - ASSA - Barkin, David. "Looking Askance at Picketty's Inequality from the Third World", 2015 (Box 36, Folder 53)
    - ASSA - Zweig, Michael. "Complicating the Labor Market as a Social Institution", 2015 (Box 36, Folder 54)
    - ASSA - Vepa, Swarna. "Child Under-weight and Agricultural Productivity in India", 2015 (Box 36, Folder 55)
- Series II. Articles Submitted for Publication to Specific RRPE Issues
  - Vol. II no.1 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Vol. II no. 2 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Vol. II no. 1 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - War and Its Impact on the Economy special issue, 1970-08 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Vol. Ill no. 1 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Vol. Ill no. 2 Paradigms. (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Vol. Ill no.3 Poverty. (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Vol. Ill no.4, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Fall
  - Vol. IV no. 1 Dependence and Foreign Domination (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Vol. IV no. 1 Dependence and Foreign Domination (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Vol. IV no. 2 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Vol. IV no. 2 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Vol. IV no. 4 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Vol. IV no. 4 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Vol. IV no. 4 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Vol. IV no. 5, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Vol. IV no. 5, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Vol. V no. 1 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Vol. V no. 1 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Vol. V no. 2 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Vol. V no. 2 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Vol. V no. 2 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Vol. XXVI (Box 15)
  - Vol. XXVII (Box 15)
  - Vol. XXVIII (Box 16)
  - Vol. XXIX (Box 16)
  - Vol. XXXI (Box 16)
  - Vol. XXXI (Box 17)
  - Vol. XXXII (Box 17)
  - Vol. XXXII (Box 18)
  - Vol. XXXIII (Box 18)
  - Vol. XXXIII (Box 19)
  - Vol. XXXIV (Box 19)
  - Vol. XXXIV (Box 20)
  - Vol. XXXVI no. 1-4 (Box 24)
  - Vol. XXXVII no. 1-4 (Box 25)
- Series III. Editorial Records of RRPE
  Miscellaneous records documenting the publication of the journal
  - Address labels, editorial board addresses, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Economic Crisis (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Articles accepted (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Letters of acknowledgement of receipt of articles (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Articles under consideration for URPE pamphlet series, [note; blank typing masters - discarded] (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - National and Newsletter Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Mayday Conference, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Initiating structure for a pamphlet series (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Summer camp, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Critiques de L'Economie Politique (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Editorial Board Memo on returning comments to readers. Editorial Board Critique sheets, Editorial Coordinator sheets Editorial Coordinator letters (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Library mailing project, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Literary clearing house letter (enclose with rejections) (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - New School Critique (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Holt agreement (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Revisals: Articles under consideration (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Warner Publications (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - RRPE miscellany, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - RRPE miscellany, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - RRPE miscellany, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - RRPE miscellany, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - RRPE miscellany, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - RRPE miscellany, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Style Sheet, 1971-10 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Editorial records, 1996-2000 (Box 6, Folder 7-8)
  - Routledge/Carfax, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Editorial Board Meeting, 1989-1993 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - JAI/Blackwell, 1996-2000 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Forms, 1983-1996 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Editorial Board Members, 1989-1992 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous Reviewing Papers, 1993-1995 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Reprint Requests, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Reprint Requests, 1980-1984 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Reprint Requests, 1985-1989 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Reprint Requests, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Imperiled Economy Reprint Requests, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Reprint Requests, 1969-1975 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Editorial Board Correspondence and Minutes, 1985-1992 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Kliman vs. Gunn Papers (I), 2000-2002 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Kliman vs. Gunn Papers (II), 2000-2002 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Kliman vs. Gunn Papers (III), 2000-2002 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Kliman vs. Gunn Papers (IV), 2000-2002 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Kliman vs. Gunn Papers (V), 2000-2002 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Printing Information, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Legal Bills, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - URPE Early History, 1969-1987 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Sage, 2002-2010 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Elections, 2003-2009 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Publisher's Report, 2005-2008 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Li Lecture, 2010 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Sherman, Howard. "Radical Economists in the 21st Century" (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Bond, Patrick. "What is Radical, in Neoliberal Nationalist South Africa?", 2011 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Dowd, Doug. "What is Coming Around the Corner", 2011 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Baker, Dean. "Getting Radical with Markets", 2012 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Fine, Ben. "Being Radical or Radical Being?", 2012 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Braunstein, Elissa. "Hybrids, Political Economy, and Macroeconomics", 2012 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Folbre, Nancy. "The Political Economy of Human Capital", 2012 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Foley, Duncan. "Rethinking Financial Capitalism", 2013 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Amin, Samir. "Audacity", 2013 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - 2013 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Topics lists, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Forms, form letters, 1996-2004 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Elsevier, 1998-2004 (Box 13, Folder 97)
  - Elsevier, 1999-2004 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Series IV. URPE Records 1969-1986
  - URPE Conference Camp Sea Gull, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Summer
  - Conference, 1969-12 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - URPE D.C. Seminars (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - URPE D.C. Seminars (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - URPE miscellany, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - General, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - URPE miscellany, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - URPE miscellany, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 8)